export const data = [
    {
      question: "Which device is required for the Internet connection?",
      option1: "Modem",
      option2: "Router",
      option3: "LAN Cable",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which continent has the highest number of countries?",
      option1: "Asia",
      option2: "Europe",
      option3: "North America",
      option4: "Africa",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Junk e-mail is also called?",
      option1: "Spam",
      option2: "Fake",
      option3: "Archived",
      option4: "Bin",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "A computer cannot BOOT if it does not have the?",
      option1: "Application Software",
      option2: "Internet",
      option3: "Operating System",
      option4: "Mouse",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "First page of Website is termed as?",
      option1: "Index Page",
      option2: "Homepage",
      option3: "Sitemap",
      option4: "Pen Drive",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "If you find a collapsed victim, what is the first thing you should do?",
      option1: "Call for help",
      option2: "Check the area for hazzards",
      option3: "Check for breathing",
      option4: "Start CPR",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "How should you open an airway in an unconscious adult victim?",
      option1: "Tilt the head back & life the chin",
      option2: "Tilt the head to the side",
      option3: "Move the tongue with your fingers",
      option4: "Tilt thee head forwards",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the maximum time you should spend checking for normal breathing?",
      option1: "5s",
      option2: "1 minute",
      option3: "2 minutes",
      option4: "10s",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "If a victim isn't breathing normally, what is the first thing you should do?",
      option1: "Call for emergency medical help and a defibailator",
      option2: "Check for a pulse in the neck",
      option3: "Give thirty chest compressions",
      option4: "Give two rescue breaths",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the correct ratio of chest compressions to rescue breaths?",
      option1: "30 to 2",
      option2: "15 to 2",
      option3: "30 to 5",
      option4: "15 to 1",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "It is acceptable to just perform chest compressions only if you are unable or not trained to deliver rescue breaths",
      option1: "True",
      option2: "False",
      option3: "None",
      option4: "---",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which is the capital of AP?",
      option1: "Amaravathi",
      option2: "vizag",
      option3: "Guntur",
      option4: "Narasapur",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How many seats got YSRCP IN 2024?",
      option1: "133",
      option2: "21",
      option3: "11",
      option4: "9",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Who the PM of India in 2024?",
      option1: "Narendra Modi",
      option2: "Apj ",
      option3: "PSPK",
      option4: "Yash",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "In the 2024 which win the ipl tropy",
      option1: "KKR",
      option2: "SRH",
      option3: "CSK",
      option4: "RCB",
      ans: 1,
    },
    
  ];